(Penny:)I think.
(Sheldon:)Did I misspeak
about the ring?
(Leonard:)Yes, and we'll get
back to that.
(Leonard:)But, uh, even with
your mother here,
(Leonard:)you are deliberately hogging
all the attention from my mom.
(Leonard:)You're like one of those
elephant seal pups
(Leonard:)that steals the milk
from two mothers!
(Sheldon:)Do you mean
what marine biologists
refer to as "super weaning"?
Yes, you are a super weaner!
(Sheldon:)Well, now I have to correct you.
A-As a bit
of an elephant seal buff,
(Sheldon:)the more accurate
comparison
(Sheldon:)would be when two mother seals
(Sheldon:)actively seek
to nourish the same pup.
(Sheldon:)So I believe the term
you're looking for
(Sheldon:)is a double mother suckler.
(Leonard:)Yeah, you're right.
(Leonard:)That is the term
I'm looking for.
(Leonard:)You are a dirty double
mother suckler!
(Sheldon:)Okay, well, now that we have the
terminology straightened out.
How dare you!